Guide to the Stanford University, Michelle R. Clayman Institute for Gender Research, Records SC0705
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Audiorecordings, Accession ARCH-2004-126
  - Lyman Lecture: Bram Dijkstra--Ideologies of Female Illness in Fin De Siecle Culture, 1986-12-3; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 12)
  - G.W.N. Lecture: Donna Haraway--Apes, Aliens, Cyborgs, and Females: Colonial Discourse and Feminist Theory, 1987-04-13; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 12)
  - Jing Lyman Lectures: Deborah L. Rhode--Justice and Gender, 1987-02-4; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 12)
  - Jing Lyman Lectures: Ruth Doell & Helen Longino--What Does Biology Have to Say About Sexual Difference?, 1987-02-11; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 12)
  - Lyman Series Winter Conference: Theoretical Perspectives on Sexual Difference: Working Session on Anthropology tape 1, 1987-02-19; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 12)
  - Lyman Series Winter Conference: Theoretical Perspectives on Sexual Difference: Working Session on Anthropology, tape 2, 1987-02-19; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 12)
  - Lyman Series Winter Conference: Theoretical Perspectives on Sexual Difference: Feminist Ethical and Political Theory 2 (2 tapes), 1987-02-19; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 12)
  - Lyman Series Winter Conference: Theoretical Perspectives on Sexual Difference: Psychological and Sociological Perspectives on Difference tape 1, 1987-02-19; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 12)
  - Lyman Series Winter Conference: Theoretical Perspectives on Sexual Difference: Psychological and Sociological Perspectives on Difference tape 2, 1987-02-19; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 12)
  - Lyman Series Winter Conference: Theoretical Perspectives on Sexual Difference: SocioBiological Theories of Difference, 1987-02-19; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 12)
  - Lyman Series Winter Conference: Theoretical Perspectives on Sexual Difference: Working Session on Feminist Theory, 1987-02-20; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 13)
  - Lyman Series Winter Conference: Theoretical Perspectives on Sexual Difference: Working Session on Feminist Theory 2, 1987-02-20; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 13)
  - Lyman Series Winter Conference: Theoretical Perspectives on Sexual Difference: Working Session on Feminist Theory 3, 1987-02-20; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 13)
  - Lyman Series Winter Conference: Theoretical Perspectives on Sexual Difference: Legal Perspectives on Sexual Difference, 1987-02-20; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 13)
  - Lyman Series Winter Conference: Theoretical Perspectives on Sexual Difference: Legal Perspectives on Sexual Difference 2, 1987-02-20; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 13)
  - Lyman Series Winter Conference: Theoretical Perspectives on Sexual Difference: Feminism and Black Political Struggle, 1987-02-20; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 13)
  - Lyman Series Winter Conference: Theoretical Perspectives on Sexual Difference: Working Session, 1987-02-21; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 13)
  - Lyman Series Winter Conference: Theoretical Perspectives on Sexual Difference: Working Session 2, 1987-02-21; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 13)
  - Lyman Lecture: Alice Kahn--Women and Humor: Unlearning Not to Offend, 1987Apr. 8; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 13)
  - Lyman Lecture: Marga Gomez--Women's Humor and Social Satire, 1987-04-22; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 13)
  - Lyman Lecture: Women's Humor and Social Satire. Regenia Gagnier--Between Women: A Cross-Class Analysis of Anarchic Humor, 1987-05-6; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 13)
  - Lyman Lecture: "Ladies Against Women" by the Plutonium Players, 1987-05-13; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 13)
  - Lyman Lecture: Suzanne Herchel at Serra House, 1987-05-19; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 13)
  - Jing Lyman International Feminism: Third World Women lecture series: opening panel, 1987 Oct 14; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 13)
  - Jing Lyman International Feminism: Third World Women lecture series: opening panel 2, 1987 Oct 14; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 13)
  - Jing Lyman International Feminism: Third World Women lecture series: [lecture] Cynthia Enloe--"Chimera of realistic strategy", 1987 Oct 21; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 13)
  - Jing Lyman International Feminism: Third World Women lecture series: Nilufer Cagatay, 1987 Oct 28; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 13)
  - Jing Lyman International Feminism:Third World Women lecture series: Christine Obbo, 1987 Nov 4; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 13)
  - Jing Lyman International Feminism: Third World Women lecture series: Sonia Alvarez, 1987 Nov 11; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 13)
  - Jing Lyman Love and Sex lectures: Hannani Kay Trask--Self Determination for Pacific Island Women, 1987-11-18; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 13)
  - Jing Lyman Love and Sex lectures: Herant Katchadourian--Sex and Intimacy in Mid-Life, 1988-02-3; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 13)
  - Associates Seminar: Nilufer Cagatay--Women in the MidEast, 1987-1988; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 13)
  - Associates Seminar: Jacobs & Shepard--Children's Literature, 1987-1988; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 13)
  - Associates Seminar: Brooks--For the Sake of a Single Phrase (Women Conductors), 1987-1988; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 13)
  - Associate's Seminar: Nadia Hijab--Arab Debate on Women, 1987-1988; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 13)
  - Associates Day 1988: Marilyn Yalom, Jing Lyman tape 1, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 13)
  - Associates Day 1988: Jing Lyman, Nan Keohane tape 2, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 13)
  - Lyman Lecture: Miriam Johnson--Fathers and Mothers and the Organization of Nurturance, 1988-02-8; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 13)
  - Jing Lyman Love and Sex Lectures: Deborah Then--The Ugly Side of Beauty: Dating Preferences and Physical Attractiveness, 1988-02-17; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 13)
  - Jing Lyman Love and Sex lectures: Nancy Stoller Shaw--AIDS Prevention and Survival Strategies, 1988-02-24; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 13)
  - Jing Lyman Love and Sex lecture: Annette Lawson--Adultery: Hers and His, 1988-03-2; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 13)
  - Jing Lyman Love and Sex Lectures: Estelle Freedman--Intimate Matters: A History of Sexuality in America, 1988-03-9; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 13)
  - Lyman Lecture: Catherine MacKinnon--Do Women Have Constitutional Rights?, 1988-04-28; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 14)
  - Lyman Lecture: Women Making Music: Tamara Brooks--The Man Who Mistook a Woman for an Artist, 1988-04-20; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 14)
  - Lyman Lecture: Women Making Music: Holly Near--Sing to Me the Dream, 1988-05-4; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 14)
  - Lyman Lecture: Women Making Music: Mary Watkins--A Chording to the People, 1988-05-11; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 14)
  - Lecture: What Does the 'Feminist' in Feminist Studies Really Mean? Diane Middlebrook, S. Matteo & J. Epstein, 1988-05-14; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 14)
  - Lyman Lecture: Women Making Music: Making a Show of It: Women, Culture, and Institutions. Panel: Ginny Berson, Penny Rosenwasser and Carmen Vazquez, 1988-05-18; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 14)
  - Corporate Seminar: Beth Milwid, Pat Millar, 1988 June 16; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 14)
  - Corporate Seminar: Pat Millar, Barbara Reskin, 1988 June 16; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 14)
  - Corporate Seminar: Mary Ann Carr, 1988-10-13; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 14)
  - Panel Discussion: Women and Power, 1988-10-26; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 14)
  - Lyman Lecture: Laura Carstensen--Is Aging a Feminist Thing?, 1988-10-12; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 14)
  - Lyman Lecture Series: Health Fair '88: Taking Action. Keynote Addresses: Deirdre English--Woman in the perspective of time/Nathan Macoby--Health Through Exercise, 1988-11-12; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 14)
  - Lyman Lecture Series: Health Fair '88: Taking Action/ Robert Marcus--Current Issues Surrounding Estrogen Replacement at Menopause, 1988-11-12; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 14)
  - Lyman Lecture Series: Health Fair '88: Taking Action [Marcus Conclusion], 1988-11-12; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 14)
  - Lyman Lecture Series: Health Fair '88: Julian Davidson--Sexuality: Women Versus Men, 1988-11-12; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 14)
  - Lyman Lecture Series: Health Fair '88: Kevin Allard--Exercise and the Busy Professional, 1988-11-12; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 14)
  - Lyman Lecture Series: Health Fair '88: Jose Cuellar--Ethnicity, Gender, and Aging, 1988-11-2; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 14)
  - Lyman Lecture Series: Health Fair '88: Linda Hawes Clever--Occupational Health from Home to Highrise, 1988-11-12; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 14)
  - Lyman Lecture Series: Health Fair '88: Freddi Kronnenberg, Sadja Greenwood - Menopause: Insights and Information, 1988-11-12; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 14)
  - Lyman Lecture Series: Health Fair '88: Kay Woodruff--Update in Decreasing Smoking, 1988-11-12; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 14)
  - Associate's Seminar: What is Feminism? #1 [panel], 1988-10-18; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 14)
  - Lyman Lecture: Kathleen McConnell--The Sandwich Generation, 1989-01-25; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 14)
  - Lyman Lecture: Michael E. Lamb--Changing Roles of Fathers, 1989-02-15; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 14)
  - Lyman Lecture: Donna J. Hitchens--Nurturing Choices, 1989-02-1; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 14)
  - Panel Discussion: Surrogate Birth- Pro or Anti Feminist? [panel], 1989-02-22; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 14)
  - Lyman Lecture: Margaret MacKenzie--The Pursuit of Self-Control part 1, 1989 Aprl 26; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 14)
  - Lyman Lecture: Margaret MacKenzie--The Pursuit of Self-Control part 2, 1989-04-26; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 14)
  - lecture: Jean Shinoda Bolen--Feminist Spirituality: Deepest and Most Significant Expression of the Women's Movement, 1989-05-10; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 14)
  - Lyman Lecture: Sanford Dornbusch--Autonomy and Control in the New Families (2 tapes), 1989-10-18; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 14)
  - Lyman Lecture: Beyond the Mommy Track. [panel] Marlene Cole, John Donahoe, Kate Walton; Myra H. Strober, moderator, 1989-10-25; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 14)
  - Lyman Lecture: Claire Brindis--Public Policy and Adolescent Pregnancy: Can We Meet the Challenge?, 1989-10-31; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 14)
  - Lyman Lecture: Edward Ziegler--Childcare: From Crisis to Solution, 1989-11-8; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 14)
  - Lyman Lecture: Annette Lawson--My Body, My Baby, My Self: The Teenage Balancing Act, 1989-11-15; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 14)
  - Corporate Seminar: Valuing Difference: Multiculturalism and the Corporate Culture. Toni Tomacci, Apple Computer Inc., 1989-12-7; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 14)
  - Associates Day 1989 tape 1: Arlene Daniels, Deborah Rhode, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 14)
  - Associates Day 1989 tape 2: Deborah Rhode, Rebecca Klatch, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 15)
  - Associate's Fall Seminar: Marilyn Yalom--Women's Memoirs of the French Revolution, 1989-10-12; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 15)
  - Associate's Winter Seminar: Sherri Matteo--Sexuality in Later Life: Myth and Reality, 1989-02-22; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 15)
  - Corporate Seminar: Strober, Rhode only (missing Miller), 1989 June 22; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 15)
  - Associates Day 1990: Barbara Babcock--Clara Shortridge Foltz: from homemaker to constitution maker. Wanda Corn & Diane Middlebrook--Psychological protraiture: the presence of the artist in the work. tape 1, 1990-01-18; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 15)
  - Associates Day 1990: Corn & Middlebrook continued tape 2, 1990-01-18; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 15)
  - Lyman Lecture: The Future of Androgyny [series] Whitney Chadwick--The Kitchen and the Bedroom: changing ideologies of femininity in 18th century French painting, 1990 Jan 31; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 15)
  - Lyman Lecture: Androgyny Conference. Barbara Gelpi--discussion on work by Sandra Bem, 1990-03-2; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 15)
  - Lyman Lecture: Jean-Marie Apostolides--Androgyny and Modernity, 1990-03-3; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 15)
  - Lyman Lecture: Discussion by Conference Participants, 1990 Mar 3; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 15)
  - 15th Anniversary IRWG Celebration: Women in the Professions [panel] tape 1, 1990-03-15; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 15)
  - 15th Anniversary IRWG Celebration: Women in the Professions [panel] tape 2, 1990-03-15; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 15)
  - Institute 15th Anniversary Celebration: Law School panel, 1990-03-15; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 15)
  - 15th Anniversary Celebration Dinner: [panel] at Faculty Club, 1990-03-15; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 15)
  - Associate's Spring Seminar: Nel Noddings--An Ethic of Caring--Beyond Decision Making, 1990-04-26; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 15)
  - Corporate Seminar: Su Schaffer--Women…Leadership…Change, 1990 Narp. 17; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 15)
  - Lyman Lecture: Candace Falk--Passion, Politics and Freedom: Emma Goldman's Legacy, 1990 Apr 25; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 15)
  - S.F. Event: tape 2, 1990 Jul 12; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 15)
  - Women's Health Research Seminar: Carl Djerassi--"Pill at 40", 1991-10-23; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 15)
  - Lyman Lecture: Diana Pearce--"Is Teenage Motherhood a Major Factor in Women's Poverty? Reflections on the Evidence", 1991 Oct 30; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 15)
  - Lyman Lecture: Michael Wald--"Drug Use by Pregnant Women--How Should Society Respond?", 1991 Nov 6; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 15)
  - Lyman Lecture: Debra Satz--"Wombs for Rent--Why Women's Reproductive Labor Should Not be a Commodity", 1991-11-13; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 15)
  - Lyman Lecture: Diana Akiyama--"Women's Bodies, Women's Lives--Sacred or Profane?", 1991-11-20; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 15)
  - Lyman Lecture: Ashley Phillips--"Feminist Frontiers: The Battle Zone Outside a Family Planning Clinic", 1991-12-4; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 15)
  - Lyman Lecture: Linda Giudice--"Ethical & Legal Issues Surrounding the Advanced Reproductive Technologies", 1991 Oct 16; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 15)
  - Lyman Lecture: Jing Lyman--"One Woman's Impressions: 33 Years of Committed Attention to Stanford by a Non-Stanford Graduate", 1991-05-8; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 15)
  - Book Party: Sexton Book Party--Diane Middlebrook, 1991-10-10; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 15)
  - lecture: Deborah Rhode, 1991-05-21; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 15)
  - lecture: William Youngs--Frankie Loves Jackie but Jackie is a Suffragist, 1991-01-23; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 15)
  - Lyman Lecture: Life After Stanford: Three Professional Women's Views of their Experiences Speakers: Kate Kelly, Helen Leong, Lisa Stelck, 1991-04-10; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 15)
  - Lyman Lecture: Rachel Bagby--"An Ecstasy of Connections: What Stanford Has Done for Me Lately", 1991-04-24; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 15)
  - Lyman Lecture: Roxanne Nilan--"Miss Lucy and Mrs. Barnes: The Failure of Co-Education at Stanford 1891-1899", 1991-05-1; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 15)
  - Lyman Lecture: Cecilia Burciaga--"Student Life at Stanford", 1991-05-15; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 15)
  - Lyman Lecture: Herant Katchadourian--"Careerism and Intellectualism Among Stanford Women", 1991-05-22; 1 audiocassette(s)
  - Lyman Lecture: Linda Hawes Clever--"Coping Strategies of Women Juggling Careers: Not to Worry, You Don't Have to Be SuperWoman", 1991-05-29; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 15)
  - Rhode (Deborah L.) Lecture: Evelyn Fox Keller--Current Perspectives on Gender and Science, 1991-05-3; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 16)
  - unknown: In Her Times: Women's History Months/20 Segments, 1991 March; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 26)
  - Associate's Day: Yanagisako, Middlebrook, Strober [two tapes], 1992-01-21; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 16)
  - Lyman Lecture: Intergenerational Perspectives on MultiCulturalism. Speakers: B. Fong, B. Taylor, W. Herriford, 1992-02-12; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 16)
  - Women's Health Research Seminar: [seminar talk] Carol Larson, 1992; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 16)
  - Women's Health Research Seminar: [seminar talk] Dolores Gallegher-Thompson, 1992-01-10; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 16)
  - Women's Health Research Seminar: Jane Zones--Breast Implants, 1992-03-24; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 16)
  - Women's Health Research Seminar: Alejandro Martinez--Gender Differences in Stanford Students' Health, 1992-04-14; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 16)
  - Women's Health Research Seminar: Carol Nadelson--Ethical Issues in Women's Health Care, 1992-04-28; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 16)
  - Women's Health Research Seminar: Iris Litt--Speaking To/With Your Doctor, 1992-05-28; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 16)
  - Women's Health Research Seminar: Carolyn Behrman--Breast Feeding in Swaziland, 1992-05-5; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 16)
  - Lyman Lecture: Iris F. Litt--Taking Our Pulse: Health of U.S. Women in the 90s [two tapes], 1992-05-2; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 16)
  - Lyman Lecture: Diana Dutton--Income, Race and Health: Legacies of the 80s, Lessons for the 90s, 1992-05-13; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 16)
  - Lyman Lecture: Nancy Adler--The Abortion Debate: Psychological Issues, 1992-04-22; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 16)
  - Lyman Lecture: Yvonne Maldonado--Epidemiologic Aspects of HIV and AIDS in Women, 1992-04-29; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 16)
  - Lyman Lecture: Madeleine Kahn--The Politics of Pornography, 1992-05-6; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 16)
  - Corporate Seminar: David Bradford, 1992June 3; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 16)
  - Corporate Seminar: Deborah Rhode--Sex at Work: Dev. Harrasment Policy, 1992-12-9; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 16)
  - Corporate Seminar: Breaking the Glass Ceiling. Myra Strober & Jay Jackman, 1992-03-1; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 16)
  - Lyman Lecture: Alice Bach, 1992-10-14; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 16)
  - Lyman Lecture: Bulbul, 1992-10-21; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 16)
  - Lyman Lecture: Student Panel with Jean Fetter, 1992-10-28; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 16)
  - Lyman Lecture: Barrie Thorne / Marilyn Yalom, 1992-11-11; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 16)
  - Lyman Lecture: Aileen Hernandez--A Revolution Deferred: The Politics of Inclusion, 1992-03-4; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 16)
  - Lyman Lecture: Deborah Rhode--Domestic Partners, 1992-02-19; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 16)
  - Lyman Lecture: Intergenerational Perspectives on MultiCulturalism, 1992-02-12; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 16)
  - Lyman Lecture: Toni Tomacci--Transitions from Campus Culture to Corporate Culture, 1992-02-5; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 16)
  - Lyman Lecture: Sharon Parker--Setting the Context for Multiculturism, 1992-01-15; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 16)
  - Lyman Lecture: Pedro Noguera--Education for the 21st Century: Meeting the Challenges of the Multicultural Classroom, 1992-01-22; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 16)
  - Associate's Day: Work and Family: Changes and Continuities, 1992-01-21; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 16)
  - Lyman Lecture: Kathy Jones--Authority and Representation: Sisterhood Is Complicated, 1992-01-29; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 16)
  - California Women's Health Agenda: Exec. Cte. Mtg. tape 1, 1992-10-14; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 16)
  - California Women's Health Agenda: Exec. Cte. Mtg. Tape 2, 1992-10-14; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 16)
  - Women's Health Research Seminar: Dalia Ducker [seminar talk], 1992-10-20; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 17)
  - Women's Health Research Seminar: Dr. H. Weinstein [seminar talk], 1992-10-27; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 17)
  - Women's Health Research Seminar: Helen Gremillion [seminar talk], 1992Nov. 19; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 17)
  - Women's Health Research Seminar: Eve Reaven [seminar talk], 1992-12-8; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 17)
  - The Spring Foundation Lecture: Resilience in Women: Dr. O'Leary interchange: Drs. Gilligan, O'Leary and Lyon, 1992-01-25; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 17)
  - The Spring Foundation Lecture: Joining the Resistance: Moments of Resilience in Women's Pysch Development. Dr. Carol Gilligan, 1992-01-25; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 17)
  - The Spring Foundation Lecture: Response and Interchange --Lisa Aspinwall, Terry Wolfer, 1992-01-25; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 17)
  - The Spring Foundation Lecture: Response and Interchange Closing Remarks. Jeanette Ickovics, 1992-01-25; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 17)
  - Associate's Day: Susan Nolan-Hoeksema--Gender Differences in Coping with Depression, 1993-01-27; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 17)
  - California Women's Health Forum: Executive Committee Meeting, 1993 January; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 17)
  - California Women's Health Forum: Women's Health Day. Iris F. Litt, 1993-11-12; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 17)
  - California Women's Health Forum: Women's Health Day. Marilyn Hansen Shaevitz, 1993-11-12; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 17)
  - California Women's Health Forum: Women's Health Day. Kate O'Hanlan, 1993-11-12; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 17)
  - California Women's Health Forum: Student Group Meeting, 1993-11-19; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 17)
  - Women's Health Research Seminar:Mary Sue Heilemann--Feminist Research with Immigrant Women, 1993-10-26; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 17)
  - Women's Health Research Seminar: Judith Barker--Health and Minority Women, 1993-11-2; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 17)
  - Women's Health Research Seminar: Bonnie Maldonado--Minority Women, AIDS, and STD's, 1993-11-9; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 17)
  - Women's Health Research Seminar: June Glenn-Lawson--Minority Women's Health --Community Clinics, 1993-11-23; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 17)
  - Women's Health Research Seminar: Carmen Portillo--Chronic Disease and Depression in Minority Women, 1993-11-30; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 17)
  - Women's Health Research Seminar: Mary Chung--Asian American Women's Health, 1993-11-7; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 17)
  - Corporate Seminar, 1993 Nov 3; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 17)
  - Leah Kaplan Lecture: Richard Lyman, speaker, 1993-10-31; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 17)
  - Lyman Lecture: Susan Bell--"The City of Ladies: Christine de Pizan's Utopian Vision", 1993-10-13; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 17)
  - Lyman Lecture: Elisabeth Hansot & Lea Wolf--Survival and Resistance in Margaret Atwood's 'The Handmaid's Tale', 1993-10-20; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 17)
  - Lyman Lecture: Ellen Peel--Beyond Utopia: Pragmatic Feminism and Narrative Energy, 1993-10-27; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 17)
  - Lyman Lecture: Mark Hall-Patton--The Founding of Halcyon, CA, 1993-11-3; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 17)
  - Lyman Lecture: Christa Johnson--Engendering Space for Utopia, 1993-11-10; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 17)
  - Lyman Lecture: Betje Black Klier--Women in Bonapartist Art and Utopian Socialist Architecture, 1993-11-17; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 17)
  - Lyman Lecture: Sally M. Gearhart--Feminism in High Drag--New Age Metaphysics, 1993-12-8; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 17)
  - Lyman Lecture: Karen Offen--European Feminism in Retrospect, 1993 Winter; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 17)
  - Lyman Lecture: Edith Gelles--Revisiting the Republican Mother, 1993 Winter; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 17)
  - Lyman Lecture: Shulamit Magnus--Gender and Feminism in Jewish Modernity, 1993 Winter; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 18)
  - Lyman Lecture: Linda Lomperis--Problems of Gender Definition and ..., 1993 Winter; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 18)
  - Lyman Lecture: Yung-Hee Kwon--The Modern Feminist Movement in Korea, 1993 Winter; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 18)
  - Lyman Lecture: Francesca Miller--Latin American Women and the Search for Social Justice, 1993 Winter; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 18)
  - Lyman Lecture: Barbara Christian--Feminist Concepts in Afro-American Writers, 1993 Winter; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 18)
  - Corporate Seminar: Constance Bagley, 1993-12-1; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 18)
  - Lyman Lecture: Wanda Corn--The Great American Thing: Georgia O'Keefe's Cow's Skull, 1993-04-14; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 18)
  - Lyman Lecture: Sherri Matteo--American Women in the Nineties, 1993-04-21; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 18)
  - Lyman Lecture: Jan Krawitz--In Our Own Image: Women and Film, 1993-04-28; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 18)
  - Lyman Lecture: Judith Brown--Florentine Nuns in the Renaissance, 1993-05-5; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 18)
  - Lyman Lecture: Will Roscoe--Gender Transgression in Ancient World, 1993-05-12; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 18)
  - Lyman Lecture: Rachel Cohon--How Surrogate Motherhood Strains Our Moral Concepts, 1993-05-19; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 18)
  - Lyman Lecture: Szonja Szelenyi--The Gender Revolution Within the Gentle Revolution, 1993 My 26; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 18)